A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 1, Series 18 FA290
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1; 171.6 Cubic Feet; 390 boxes, 532 microfilm reels
  - Commonwealth Fund - Fellowship Appropriations, June 10, 1930 (Box 85, Folder 782)
  - Commonwealth Fund-Carnegie Corporation - Discussion Program on Education and Health Care - Interfoundation Meetings on Health Services and Medical Education, 1967-1973 (Box 85, Folder 783)
  - Commonwealth Fund-Carnegie Corporation - Discussion Program on Education and Health Care - Neighborhood Community Health Center, April-June, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 784)
  - Commonwealth Fund-Carnegie Corporation - Exploratory Conference on Medical Services and Medical Education, January-March, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 785)
  - Commonwealth Fund-Carnegie Corporation - Exploratory Conference on Medical Services and Medical Education, March-December, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 786)
  - Commonwealth Fund-Carnegie Corporation - Exploratory Conference on Medical Services and Medical Education, March-December, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 787)
  - Commonwealth Fund-Carnegie Corporation - Exploratory Conference on Medical Services and Medical Education - Report - "The Crisis in Medical Services and Medical Education", October 1966 (Box 86, Folder 788)
  - Commonwealth Fund-Carnegie Corporation - Feasibility Study of Forming a University-Based Study Center on Medical Services and Medical Education (ME&CH), 1966-1968 (Box 86, Folder 789)
  - Commonwealth Fund-Carnegie Corporation - Study to Consider the National Problem of Financing Medical Education, 1966-1973 (Box 86, Folder 790)
  - Commonwealth Fund-Carnegie Corporation - Study to Consider the National Problem of Financing Medical Education, 1966-1973 (Box 86, Folder 791)
  - Commonwealth Fund-Carnegie Corporation - Working Conference on Behavioral Sciences and Medical Education (ME&CH), 1966-1969 (Box 86, Folder 792)
  - Commonwealth Fund-Carnegie Corporation - Working Conference on Behavioral Sciences and Medical Education (ME&CH), 1966-1969 (Box 86, Folder 793)
  - Community Blood Council of Greater New York, Inc. - Construction or Renovation of Facilities for Service, Research and Education, 1973-1975 (Box 87, Folder 794)
  - Community Blood Council of Greater New York, Inc. - New York Blood Center and Research Institute (ME&CH), 1960-1972 (Box 87, Folder 795)
  - Community Blood Council of Greater New York, Inc. - New York Blood Center and Research Institute (ME&CH), 1960-1972 (Box 87, Folder 796)
  - Community Blood Council of Greater New York, Inc. - New York Blood Center and Research Institute (ME&CH), 1960-1972 (Box 87, Folder 797)
  - Community Service Society of New York - Experiment to Rehabilitate Dependent Families, 1966-1971 (Box 87, Folder 798)
  - Community Service Society of New York - Experiment to Rehabilitate Dependent Families - Publications, 1949-1970 (Box 87, Folder 799)
  - Community Service Society of New York - Experiment to Rehabilitate Dependent Families - Publications, 1949-1970 (Box 87, Folder 800)
  - The Conference Board - Corporations and Health Care and Invitational Conference on Industry Roles in Health Care, 1971-1974 (Box 88, Folder 801)
  - Conference of State and Provincial Health Authorities - Field Unit for Record Service to State Health Departments, 1939-1942 (Box 88, Folder 802)
  - Connecticut Society for Mental Hygiene, 1928-1930 (Box 88, Folder 803)
  - University of Connecticut (Health Center) - Study of Knowledge-Performance Gap Among Physicians, 1975-1979 (Box 88, Folder 804)
  - University of Connecticut (Health Center) - Study of Knowledge-Performance Gap Among Physicians, 1975-1979 (Box 88, Folder 805)
  - University of Connecticut (Health Center) - Study of Knowledge-Performance Gap Among Physicians, 1975-1979 (Box 88, Folder 806)
  - University of Connecticut (Health Center) - Study of Knowledge-Performance Gap Among Physicians - Report - "Core Goals and Objectives of the University of Connecticut School of Medicine: The Product and the Process", August 1975 (Box 88, Folder 807)
  - Consultant on Community Services (EHS), May-September, 1949 (Box 88, Folder 808)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1951-1952 (Box 88, Folder 809)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1951-1952 (Box 88, Folder 810)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1952-1954 (Box 89, Folder 811)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1952-1954 (Box 89, Folder 812)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1952-1954 (Box 89, Folder 813)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1952-1954 (Box 89, Folder 814)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1952-1954 (Box 89, Folder 815)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1952-1954 (Box 89, Folder 816)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1952-1954 (Box 89, Folder 817)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1952-1954 (Box 89, Folder 818)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1954-1959 (Box 90, Folder 819)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1954-1959 (Box 90, Folder 820)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1954-1959 (Box 90, Folder 821)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1954-1959 (Box 90, Folder 822)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1954-1959 (Box 90, Folder 823)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1954-1959 (Box 90, Folder 824)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1954-1959 (Box 90, Folder 825)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1959-1972 (Box 91, Folder 826)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1959-1972 (Box 91, Folder 827)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1959-1972 (Box 91, Folder 828)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program (ME), 1959-1972 (Box 91, Folder 829)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Comprehensive Care and Teaching Program - "Toward Better Nursing Care of Patients with Long-Term Illness", 1956 (Box 91, Folder 830)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Joint Program with the University of Bahia, Brazil (ME&CH), 1964-1970 (Box 91, Folder 831)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Joint Program with the University of Bahia, Brazil (ME&CH), 1964-1970 (Box 91, Folder 832)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Joint Program with the University of Bahia, Brazil (ME&CH), 1964-1970 (Box 91, Folder 833)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Joint Program with the University of Bahia, Brazil (ME&CH), 1970-1976 (Box 92, Folder 834)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Joint Program with the University of Bahia, Brazil - Annual Reports (ME&CH), 1964-1966 (Box 92, Folder 835)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Joint Program with the University of Bahia, Brazil - Annual Reports (ME&CH), 1964-1966 (Box 92, Folder 836)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Pilot Clinic for Broader Medical Service (ME), 1945-1955 (Box 92, Folder 837)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Pilot Clinic for Broader Medical Service (ME), 1945-1955 (Box 92, Folder 838)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Pilot Clinic for Broader Medical Service (ME), 1945-1955 (Box 92, Folder 839)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Pilot Clinic for Broader Medical Service - Financial Data (ME), 1946-1951 (Box 92, Folder 840)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Study of Blood Fats in Relation to Arteriosclerosis (MR), 1950-1953 (Box 92, Folder 841)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Study of Diagnostic Uses of the Vaginal Smear, 1940-1943 (Box 92, Folder 842)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Study of Diagnostic Uses of the Vaginal Smear, 1944-1946 (Box 93, Folder 843)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Study of Diagnostic Uses of the Vaginal Smear - Financial Data, 1940-1947 (Box 93, Folder 844)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Study of Diagnostic Uses of the Vaginal Smear - Financial Data, 1940-1947 (Box 93, Folder 845)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Study of Exfoliated Normal and Cancer Cells, 1946-1953 (Box 93, Folder 846)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Study of Exfoliated Normal and Cancer Cells, 1946-1953 (Box 93, Folder 847)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Study of Exfoliated Normal and Cancer Cells - Financial Data, 1946-1954 (Box 93, Folder 848)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Training of Allied Health Personnel to Assist Surgeons in Hospital Care, 1971-1977 (Box 93, Folder 849)
  - Cornell University/Rockefeller University - Coordinated MD/Ph.D. Program, 1971-1972 (Box 93, Folder 850)
  - Cornell University/Rockefeller University - Coordinated MD/Ph.D. Program, 1973-1980 (Box 94, Folder 851)
  - Cornell University/Rockefeller University - Coordinated MD/Ph.D. Program, 1973-1980 (Box 94, Folder 852)
  - Council on Foundations, Inc. - General Support, 1981-1982 (Box 94, Folder 853)
  - Council on Foundations, Inc. - Public Affairs and Education Program, 1972-1977 (Box 94, Folder 854)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc. - Comprehensive Bibliographic System for Research Libraries, 1978-1981 (Box 94, Folder 855)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc. - Comprehensive Bibliographic System for Research Libraries, 1978-1981 (Box 94, Folder 856)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc. - Comprehensive Bibliographic System for Research Libraries, 1978-1981 (Box 94, Folder 857)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc. - Comprehensive Bibliographic System for Research Libraries, 1978-1981 (Box 94, Folder 858)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc. - Comprehensive Bibliographic System for Research Libraries, 1978-1981 (Box 94, Folder 859)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc. - Comprehensive Bibliographic System for Research Libraries, 1978-1981 (Box 94, Folder 860)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc. - Comprehensive Bibliographic System for Research Libraries, 1981-1983 (Box 95, Folder 861)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc. - Comprehensive Bibliographic System for Research Libraries, 1981-1983 (Box 95, Folder 862)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc. - Comprehensive Bibliographic System for Research Libraries, 1981-1983 (Box 95, Folder 863)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc. - Comprehensive Bibliographic System for Research Libraries, 1981-1983 (Box 95, Folder 864)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc. - Study of the Technical and Administrative Requirements of a National Periodicals Center, 1977-1979 (Box 95, Folder 865)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc. - Study of the Technical and Administrative Requirements of a National Periodicals Center, 1977-1979 (Box 95, Folder 866)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc. - Study of the Technical and Administrative Requirements of a National Periodicals Center, 1977-1979 (Box 95, Folder 867)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc. - Study of the Technical and Administrative Requirements of a National Periodicals Center, 1977-1979 (Box 95, Folder 868)
  - Dallas Child Guidance Clinic - Fellowship, 1926-1927 (Box 96, Folder 869)
  - Dartmouth College (Library) - Convocation, Publication and Distribution of "American Libraries as Centers of Scholarship", 1978-1979 (Box 96, Folder 870)
  - Dartmouth College (Research Center/Veterans Administration Center/Psychiatry Service), 1979-1981 (Box 96, Folder 871)
  - Dartmouth College and Medical School - Program of Counselling Undergraduate Students Preparing for Medical or Health Careers, 1968-1976 (Box 96, Folder 872)
  - Dartmouth College and Medical School - Program of Counselling Undergraduate Students Preparing for Medical or Health Careers, 1968-1976 (Box 96, Folder 873)
  - Dartmouth Medical School - Establishment of a Four Year Medical Curriculum (ME&CH), 1967-1972 (Box 96, Folder 874)
  - Dartmouth Medical School - Establishment of a Four Year Medical Curriculum (ME&CH), 1967-1972 (Box 96, Folder 875)
  - Dartmouth Medical School - Establishment of a Four Year Medical Curriculum - Auxiliary Publications (ME&CH), 1962-1969 (Box 96, Folder 876)
  - Dartmouth Medical School - Establishment of a Full-Time Department of Medicine (ME&CH), 1963-1966 (Box 96, Folder 877)
  - Dartmouth Medical School - Refounding of the Medical School (ME&CH), January-December, 1956 (Box 96, Folder 878)
  - Dartmouth Medical School - Refounding of the Medical School (ME&CH), 1957-1970 (Box 97, Folder 879)
  - Dartmouth Medical School - Refounding of the Medical School (ME&CH), 1957-1970 (Box 97, Folder 880)
  - Dartmouth Medical School - Refounding of the Medical School (ME&CH), 1957-1970 (Box 97, Folder 881)
  - Dartmouth Medical School - Refounding of the Medical School (ME&CH), 1957-1970 (Box 97, Folder 882)
  - Dartmouth Medical School - Refounding of the Medical School (ME&CH), 1957-1970 (Box 97, Folder 883)
  - Dartmouth Medical School - Refounding of the Medical School (ME&CH), 1957-1970 (Box 97, Folder 884)
  - Dartmouth Medical School - Refounding of the Medical School - Auxiliary Publications, 1955-1957 (Box 97, Folder 885)
  - Downstate Medical Center - Conference on the Paraprofessional Health Sphere, April-September, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 886)
  - Downstate Medical Center - Renewal Support for the Training of Nurses/Midwives, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 887)
    See Commonwealth Fund, Grant Series, Maternity Center Association, Box 190-191, Folders 1786-1792.
  - Drew Postgraduate Medical School - Planning Program for the Development of a Community-based Academic Medical Center, April-May, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 888)
  - Drew Postgraduate Medical School - Planning Program for the Development of a Community-based Academic Medical Center, 1970-1976 (Box 98, Folder 889)
  - Drew Postgraduate Medical School - Planning Program for the Development of a Community-based Academic Medical Center - Reports, 1967-1973 (Box 98, Folder 890)
  - Drew Postgraduate Medical School - Planning Program for the Development of a Community-based Academic Medical Center - Reports, 1967-1973 (Box 98, Folder 891)
  - Drew Postgraduate Medical School - Planning Program for the Development of a Community-based Academic Medical Center - Reports, 1967-1973 (Box 98, Folder 892)
  - Drew Postgraduate Medical School - Planning Program for the Development of a Community-based Academic Medical Center - Reports, 1967-1973 (Box 98, Folder 893)
  - Drew Postgraduate Medical School - Planning Program for the Development of a Community-based Academic Medical Center - Reports, 1967-1973 (Box 98, Folder 894)
  - Drew Postgraduate Medical School - Planning Program for the Development of a Community-based Academic Medical Center - Reports, 1967-1973 (Box 98, Folder 895)
  - Drew Postgraduate Medical School - Planning Program for the Development of a Community-based Academic Medical Center - Reports, 1967-1973 (Box 98, Folder 896)
  - Drug Abuse Council, Inc. - Annual Reports, 1972, 1973, 1976 (Box 98, Folder 897)
  - Drug Abuse Council, Inc. - Founding of the Council, October-November, 1970 (Box 98, Folder 898)
  - Drug Abuse Council, Inc. - Founding of the Council, 1971-1974 (Box 99, Folder 899)
  - Drug Abuse Council, Inc. - Founding of the Council, 1971-1974 (Box 99, Folder 900)
  - Drug Abuse Council, Inc. - Founding of the Council, 1971-1974 (Box 99, Folder 901)
  - Drug Abuse Council, Inc. - Founding of the Council, 1971-1974 (Box 99, Folder 902)
  - Drug Abuse Council, Inc. - Planning Project Underlying the Formation of the Council and the Design of its Initial Program, May-November, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 903)
  - Drug Abuse Council, Inc. - Support of the Final Two Years of the Council's Operation, 1974-1979 (Box 99, Folder 904)
  - Drug Abuse Council, Inc. - Support of the Final Two Years of the Council's Operation, 1974-1979 (Box 99, Folder 905)
  - Duke University Center for the Study of Health Policy - Funds for Establishment, 1972-1979 (Box 99, Folder 906)
  - Duke University Center for the Study of Health Policy - Funds for Establishment, 1972-1979 (Box 99, Folder 907)
  - Duke University Center for the Study of Health Policy - Renewed support, 1977-1982 (Box 100, Folder 908)
  - Duke University Medical Center - Bioengineering and Computer Science Fund, March-December, 1980 (Box 100, Folder 909)
  - Duke University Medical Center - Conferences on Leadership for Women in Medicine and Minority Women in Medicine, 1980-1981 (Box 100, Folder 910)
  - Duke University Medical Center - Experimental Program in Training Unskilled Women for Services in the Health Field, 1969-1974 (Box 100, Folder 911)
  - Duke University Medical Center - Future of Biomedical Education (Symposium and Publication), 1969-1974 (Box 100, Folder 912)
  - Duke University Medical Center - Future of Biomedical Education (Symposium and Publication), 1969-1974 (Box 100, Folder 913)
  - Duke University Medical Center - Future of Biomedical Education (Symposium and Publication), 1969-1974 (Box 100, Folder 914)
  - Duke University Medical Center - New Curriculum (ME&CH), 1964-1975 (Box 100, Folder 915)
  - Duke University Medical Center - New Curriculum (ME&CH), 1964-1975 (Box 100, Folder 916)
  - Duke University Medical Center - New Curriculum (ME&CH), 1964-1975 (Box 100, Folder 917)
  - Duke University Medical Center - New Curriculum - Report - "Development Program1964-1970" (ME&CH), August 1, 1964 (Box 101, Folder 918)
  - Duke University School of Medicine - Experiment in Training and Use of Physicians Assistants (ME&CH), 1969-1974 (Box 101, Folder 919)
  - Duke University School of Medicine - Experiment in Training and Use of Physicians Assistants (ME&CH), 1969-1974 (Box 101, Folder 920)
  - Duke University School of Medicine - Experiment in Training and Use of Physicians Assistants - Auxiliary Reports (ME&CH), 1969-1971 (Box 101, Folder 921)
  - Duke University School of Medicine - Experiment in Training and Use of Physicians Assistants - Auxiliary Reports (ME&CH), 1969-1971 (Box 101, Folder 922)
  - Duke University School of Medicine - Experimental Training Program in the Basic Medical Sciences (ME&CH), 1955-1972 (Box 101, Folder 923)
  - Duke University School of Medicine - Experimental Training Program in the Basic Medical Sciences (ME&CH), 1955-1972 (Box 101, Folder 924)
  - Duke University School of Medicine - Experimental Training Program in the Basic Medical Sciences (ME&CH), 1955-1972 (Box 101, Folder 925)
  - Duke University School of Medicine - Teaching, Research and Demonstration in the Health-Care Field (ME&CH), 1967-1974 (Box 102, Folder 926)
  - Duke University School of Medicine - Teaching, Research and Demonstration in the Health-Care Field (ME&CH), 1967-1974 (Box 102, Folder 927)
  - Duke University School of Medicine - Teaching, Research and Demonstration in the Health-Care Field - Auxiliary Reports (ME&CH), 1967 (Box 102, Folder 928)
  - Economic Development Council of New York City, Inc. - General Support, 1977-1982 (Box 102, Folder 929)
  - Economic Development Council of New York City, Inc. - General Support, 1977-1982 (Box 102, Folder 930)
  - Education and World Affairs - Study of the International Migration of Talent, 1967-1970 (Box 102, Folder 931)
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (WNET/Channel 13) - General Support, 1979-1983 (Box 102, Folder 932)
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (WNET/Channel 13) - General Support, 1979-1983 (Box 102, Folder 933)
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (WNET/Channel 13) - Programing on Medicine and Health, 1965-1970 (Box 103, Folder 934)
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (WNET/Channel 13) - Support for Major Capital and Program Development, 1975-1978 (Box 103, Folder 935)
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (WNET/Channel 13) - Support for Major Capital and Program Development, 1975-1978 (Box 103, Folder 936)
  - Einstein College of Medicine - Evaluation and Modification of the Program of Medical Education (ME&CH), 1965-1970 (Box 103, Folder 937)
  - Einstein College of Medicine - Health Careers Program at Lincoln Hospital (ME&CH), 1966-1974 (Box 103, Folder 938)
  - Einstein College of Medicine - Health Careers Program at Lincoln Hospital (ME&CH), 1966-1974 (Box 103, Folder 939)
  - Einstein College of Medicine - Health Careers Program at Lincoln Hospital (ME&CH), 1966-1974 (Box 103, Folder 940)
  - Einstein College of Medicine - Health Careers Program at Lincoln Hospital (ME&CH), 1966-1974 (Box 103, Folder 941)
  - Einstein College of Medicine - Program with the New Medical School at Rotterdam, Netherlands (ME&CH), 1967-1970 (Box 103, Folder 942)
  - Einstein College of Medicine - Program with the New Medical School at Rotterdam, Netherlands (ME&CH), 1971-1978 (Box 104, Folder 943)
  - Emory University School of Medicine - Fellowships in Population Control and Family Planning, 1965-1967 (Box 104, Folder 944)
  - Encounter Limited-Freedom House - Emergency Operating Support, 1976-1983 (Box 104, Folder 945)
  - English-Speaking Union of the United States - King George VI Memorial Fund, 1952-1957 (Box 104, Folder 946)
  - The Exploratorium - Program in Science Education and General Support, 1976-1980 (Box 104, Folder 947)
  - Eye-Bank for Sight Restoration - Electron Microscope, 1956-1959 (Box 104, Folder 948)
  - Family Welfare Association of America, 1919-1921; June 10, 1931 (Box 104, Folder 949)
  - Family Welfare Societies of New York - Relief Appropriation, 1938-1940 (Box 104, Folder 950)
  - Farmers Federation Educational and Development Fund - Health Insurance in North Carolina (EHS), 1950-1952 (Box 104, Folder 951)
  - Farmers Federation Educational and Development Fund - Health Insurance in North Carolina (EHS), 1950-1952 (Box 104, Folder 952)
  - Farmers Federation Educational and Development Fund - Health Insurance in North Carolina (EHS), 1952-1964 (Box 105, Folder 953)
  - Farmers Federation Educational and Development Fund - Health Insurance in North Carolina (EHS), 1952-1964 (Box 105, Folder 954)
  - Farmers Federation Educational and Development Fund - Health Insurance in North Carolina (EHS), 1952-1964 (Box 105, Folder 955)
  - Fellowship Center, Inc. - Problem of Alcoholism Among Inmates of the Correctional System, 1979-1981 (Box 105, Folder 956)
  - Fisk University - Conference between Representatives of the United Negro College Fund and the Association of American Medical Colleges (July 13-15, 1975), 1975-1976 (Box 105, Folder 957)
  - University of Florida - Planning for New Medical School (ME), 1950-1952 (Box 105, Folder 958)
  - University of Florida - Planning for New Medical School (ME), 1950-1952 (Box 105, Folder 959)
  - University of Florida - Planning for New Medical School (ME), 1950-1952 (Box 105, Folder 960)
  - University of Florida - Planning for New Medical School (ME), 1950-1952 (Box 105, Folder 961)
  - University of Florida - Planning for New Medical School (ME), 1952-1954 (Box 106, Folder 962)
  - University of Florida - Planning for New Medical School (ME), 1952-1954 (Box 106, Folder 963)
  - University of Florida - Planning for New Medical School (ME), 1952-1954 (Box 106, Folder 964)
  - University of Florida - Planning for New Medical School (ME), 1952-1954 (Box 106, Folder 965)